Hello Hello, I'm from the city of
Здравствуйте Здравствуйте я из города
Khmelnitsky Where are you from? I'm from
Хмельницкий Вы откуда Я из
Moscow, so cheerful, from Moscow,
Москвы такие весёленькие из Москвы
usually everyone is boring, so serious, from
обычно все скучные такие серьёзные из
Moscow, from Moscow.
Москвы из Москвы
No, it seems to me by your face that you're from the
Нет мне кажется вот по лицу что вы из
Urals, not exactly from Moscow. I was directly
Урала нене точно из Москвы Я прямо
born in Moscow. And my
родился в Москве А
parents. Parents from the Moscow region, and my
родители Родители из Подмосковья а
grandmother.
бабушка
Grandfather is also from the Moscow region Well, we’re all from
дедушка тоже из Подмосковье Ну все Мы
here Well, anyway, someone somewhere in the
отсюда Ну всё равно кто-то где-то в
Moscow region came from Well, maybe
Подмосковье приехал откуда Ну возможно
someone came once I already had my own
кто-то когда-то приехал я уж своё вот
tree, well, I haven’t studied it well,
это вот ну дерево как это ну не изучал
so I understood, I
вот настолько понял
understood What are you  studied
понял А что вы изучали
uh school this as his school
ээ школьный этот как его школьную
curriculum also studied the school curriculum
программу ещё изучили школьную программу
Yes, not
Да не
very much, but
очень
you studied the school curriculum a
а вы сильно изучили школьную программу
lot Well, okay Okay And who did you study to become a
сильно Ну хорошо Окей А на кого учились
programmer after school after school And then also to become a
программиста А потом ещё на
lawyer Well, okay, then you
юриста Ну хорошо значит закон
know the law I heard this then  the question is
знаете Слышал тогда тогда такой вопрос
how do you treat the Minsk
как относитесь к минским
agreements as a signed
соглашениям как к подписанному
agreement that Russia did not fulfill
договору который Россия не выполнила Да
Yes and Why Russia did not comply Well because
а Почему Россия не выполнила Ну потому
Russia did not comply We come in and
что Россия не выполнила Мы заходим
look I, as a lawyer, come in and look at the
смотрите Я как юрист захожу и смотрю
parliamentary documents uh the
документы парламентской вот
Minsk agreements were signed by a
эээ минские соглашения подписывала ри
trilateral group yes this is Russia
трёхсторонняя группа да это Россия
Ukraine and  The OSCE was the arbiter in this
Украина и обсе обсе было арбитром в этой
whole situation, and so the
всей ситуации так вот парламентская
OSCE Parliamentary Assembly, in its
Ассамблея обсе в своих ээ декларациях
annual declarations, indicated every year that
годовых так каждый год обозначало что
Russia does not fulfill its
Россия не исполняет свои
obligations under the Minsk agreements
обязательства по минским соглашениям
taken. So, this is in the declarations in the
взятых Так а это в декларациях в
declarations. Yes, but there is
декларациях Да а вот есть
also, as you say, the UN yes
ещё как вы говорите вот ООН да
correct And the OSCE OSCE is
правильно А обсе обсе
correct in the OSCE there is a daily report
правильно в обсе есть каждодневный отчёт
Yes, there is a daily report there, roughly
Да вот каждодневный отчёт там грубо
speaking, well, for every day
говоря вот ну на каждый день
there is
есть
not a violation of all this, what
не нарушение вот этого всего то что в
was spelled out in the Minsk agreement And it was
Минске соглашении было прописано И вот
precisely on a daily basis that nothing was
именно в каждодневно ничего не было
recorded
зафиксировано
Which, especially since Russia violated  what is this
Что тем более Россия нарушила потому что
mins sog on cam on which on which
это минс сог на кам на каком на каком
site I understood on the cam site Wait On On
сайте я понял на кам сайте Подожди На На
what site did you read these daily
каком сайте вы читали эти ежедневные
otts
отты
if I tell you I haven’t read anything
если вам сказать я не читал ничего
like that I’m sure I’m just sure
такого нечи я вот уверен я просто уверен
look Dude I’m sure you’re not that  I have
смотри Чувак я уверен что ты не то что
n’t read the OSCE reports You’ve never read anything in your life
отчёты обсе не читал Ты в жизни ничего
You’ve never read
не читал Ты в жизни вообще не читал
the instructions on toilet paper in your life Yes, this is a
инструкцию на туалетной бумаг Да это
direct insult, veiled Yes, but
прямое оскорбление завуалировано Да но
just like that Well, don’t look, I didn’t, I
прямо так Ну ну я не смотри я не я мог я
could have said it more rudely I said
мог бы сказать более грубо Я сказал Вот
You’re stupid, that’s it  there was an insult And that’s what I
вы тупой это было оскорбление А так я
said. It seems to me that in your life it’s not
сказал Вот мне кажется что вы в жизни не
just that you haven’t read the OSCE reports, but that is,
то что не читали отчёты обсе да Ну вот
you haven’t studied the school curriculum
то есть школьную программу вы не выучили
and the reports. Where did you hear about the OSCE reports? Yes,
а отчёты Откуда Вы слышали про отчёты
from all sorts of news, or that is, they
обсе Да из всяких новостей а то есть вам
told you on TV that  there were some
по телевизору сказали что были какие-то
OSCE reports Well, well, not on TV Okay
отчёты обсе Да ну не по телевизору Окей
And where where Well, let’s say some
А где где Ну у блогеров допустим какой
blogger told you that there were reports, you
блогер вам рассказал что были отчёты вы
read all the OS reports No, look,
читали все отчёты ос Нет смотрите я
look again, when I talk about
смотрите ещё раз я когда говорю про
declarations, I can now open it for you and
декларации могу сейчас вам открыть и
tell you specifically the declarations  and read
сказать конкретно декларации и прочитать
excerpts from them Yes, the declaration - What is this?
из них выдержки Да декларация - Это что
This is an opinion
такое Это мнение
of some kind; this is not true. Based on all the
какого-то это на нет На основании всех
daily reports, they make an
отчётов каждодневных делают декларацию
annual declaration. Yes, and what is written there that Russia
годовую Да и что там написано что Россия
did not comply?  you
Давайте только мне непонятно Вот вы себя
consider yourself an intelligent person and you say
считаете умным человеком и говорите ну
such complete nonsense Why nonsense because the
такую полную дичь Почему дичь потому что
Minsk agreements were between Ukraine,
минские соглашения были между Украиной
Donetsk and Lugansk regions of Russia there
Донецкой и Луганской областью России там
for a minute, for a minute, you once in your life
бля на минуту минуту вы когда-то в жизни
opened a document with the Minsk
открывали документ с минскими
agreements, I read it, and I read there
соглашениями я его Читал да там читал
what it’s called  What is the name of this
как он называется Как называется Этот
document
документ
Oh [ __ ], now open it Well Open
Ой [__] ну сейчас открыть Ну Откройте
Well seriously
Ну серьёзно
Open it you thought
Откройте вы вы считали вот
you read it yes young man I read it you
вы читали да молодой человек я читал вы
read it yes what the name is the Minsk
читали да как на Как называются минские
agreements what they are called what
соглашения как они называются как
the document
документ
is called I have to
называется мне обязательно это
remember this I think if you read it you
запоминать Я думаю если вы читали вы
some details there You say
какие-то такие детали там Говорите
that are not there, then I think what
которых там нет то я думаю то что там
was there you would definitely remember the name of the
было вы бы точно запомнили название
document you would
документа вы бы
remember the document on a set of measures to
запомнили документ о комплексе мер по
implement the Minsk agreements this is not no no no no
выполнению минских соглашения это не нет
you opened something no
нет нет нет вы не то открыли нет
Open First you opened the document  about
Откройте Сначала вы открыли документ о
the implementation of Yes the Minsk agreements And here are the
выполнении Да минских соглашений А вот
Minsk agreements Open What
минские соглашения Откройте Как
is the name of the protocol text
называется там протокол текст да
yes yes Here I
да Вот я его
opened it I have it just for
открыл У меня есть как раз для
special ones for such people who
специальных для таких людей которые
did not go through the school program I
школьную программу не проходили У меня
have a selection of
есть подборочка
no Listen buddy If you yes yes
не Слушай дружище Если ты будешь да да
call names you know  don’t run away don’t
обзываться знаешь не убегайте не
run away Find find I want I [ __ ]
убегайте Найдите найдите Я хочу я [__]
something
чтото
wed you’re already [ __ ] Find you’re doing everything
сре ты уже срешь Найди ты всё делаешь
So as not to look you’re doing everything So as not to
Чтобы не искать ты всё делаешь Чтобы не
look You can’t
искать Ты уже не можешь найти тебе
find anymore You don’t have enough school knowledge to find
школьных знаний не хватает чтобы найти
Nagulino with measures A set of measures to
нагулино с мер комплекс мер по
implement the Minsk agreements here  it means that
выполнению минских соглашени вот значит
there were Minsk agreements, a set of measures for
были минские соглашения комплекс мер по
their implementation. It’s true. So before that there
их выполнению правда Значит до этого ещё
were also Minsk agreements. Find these
были минские соглашения Найди эти
Minsk agreements that were based on
минские соглашения которые были по
which a set of measures were then adopted. And
которым потом принимался комплекс мер А
you mean, well, you read
вы имеете в виду ну ты же прочитал
the set of measures for the implementation of the Minsk
комплекс мер по выполнению минских
agreements. Well, the
соглашений Ну
first and second ones are not there.  there are
они нету первых и вторых есть
some and the second is a set of measures for the
одни а второе - это комплекс мер по
implementation of the Minsk agreements, it’s
выполнению минских соглашений он же так
called that. You read it, it doesn’t
и называется Вы же прочитали там же не
say that some agreements are
сказано что какие-то соглашения
additional Yes, this is a set of measures Yes for the
дополнительные Да это комплекс мер Да по
implementation of those Minsk agreements Come on
выполнению тех минских соглашений А ну
badge It’s been so long since I’ve been gone
давай бляха Как давно уже не было Я
I think those witnesses from Minsk have already disappeared,
думаю те уже перевелись свидетели Минска
in short, but here the new guy is a year late
короче а вот тут новый чувак на год
Well, we’ll have to talk
опоздал Ну придётся поговорить
Let’s, yes, yes, I’ll
Давайте да да
find it now if, as you say,
найду если у нас ещё как ты говоришь за
they haven’t disappeared in a year,
год они не
and I’m talking about the
а я вам об
implementation of the provisions of the protocol based on the results of the
исполнении положений протокола по итогам
consultation, trilateral contact, this is
консультации трёхсторонний контакт вот
it  I don’t know You’re somehow
это вот я не знаю Вы как-то обрывка
dreaming of a fragment Read what’s written on top yes
мечтаете Прочитайте сверху что
nothing is written on top
написано да сверху ничего ме написано
it’s pictures b m in the picture there’s something
это картин б м в картинке что-то
written on top at they if it’s a picture of
написано сверху у тея если это картинка
the text
текста
a memorandum on execution you
меморандум по исполнению ты имеешь в
mean this No no don’t find the memorandum
виду вот это Нет не меморандум не найди
These are the Minsk agreements, after all,
вот эти минские соглашения всё-таки
with which it all
с которых всё
began You can
началось Ты же такой так можешь
read it like that or something like that I want
прочитать или что так Я хочу чтобы ты
you to do it I want to teach you to teach
это сделал Я тебя хочу научить научить
Google Come on No,
Гугли Давай Нет
you can’t [ __ ] find it, you’ll run away I
[__] ты не сможешь найти ты убежишь Я
said I can see it in your eyes  I
сказал я это я вижу по твоим глазам я
see in your eyes the pain in your eyes
вижу по твоим глазам боль в твоих глазах
you understand your confusion that you
ты понимаешь свою растерянность что ты
won’t find it in life you understand you’re like that you’ve
не Найдёшь её в жизни понимаешь ты такой
never opened it in your life you’re
ты никогда его в жизни не открывал ты
like that now [ __ ] where did I
такой сейчас [__] где я это
hear that And I’m enjoying it I’m like that I’m
слышал А я наслаждаюсь я такой значишь Я
like an energy vampire I’m being sucked out
как вампир энергетический я высасывают
your vital juices at this moment I’m
твои жизненные соки в этот момент я
watching you, in short, it means Czech I’m and I’m
смотрю как ты короче значит чех я а я
enjoying the memorandum on the implementation of the
кайфую меморандум об исполнении
provisions of the protocol following the
положений протокола по итогам
consultation tripartite contact Group
консультации трёхсторонний контак Груп
related
относящийся
this is not the same regarding the steps
это не то относительно шагов
aimed at all this some kind of
направленных на всё всё это какой-то ты
memorandum you found don’t find the Minsk
меморандум нашёл не найди минские
agreements A  I’m
соглашения А я покайфу
just enjoying it, you’re [ __ ] something that’s there for you to
просто да ты [__] что-то что там тебе
get high [ __ ], I’m really getting high Yes,
кайфовать Бля я реально кайфую
I see your pain and wait,
Да я вижу боль твои а подожди комплекс
you already said a set of measures to implement the mines
мер по выполнению мин были ты уже
No, this is Look, this is a set of measures
говорил Нет это Смотри это комплекс мер
to implement the Minsk
по выполнению минских
agreements Minsky again, you yourself
соглашений Минский ещё раз ты сам
read
прочитал
it  on the implementation of the Minsk agreements Come
смо по выполнению минских соглашений Ну
on, it’s written the truth You yourself
же написано правда Ты же сам своим ртом
read with your own mouth a set of measures for the implementation of the
прочитал комплекс мер по выполнению
Minsk agreements, that is, there were
минских соглашений то есть значит были
Minsk agreements they signed Yes, the Minsk
минские соглашения они подпис Да минские
agreements are a complex of
соглашения это комплекс р
p but now some kind of complex of p
по а теперь какой-то комплекс р бы
Read the Minsk agreements Let’s start
Прочитай минские соглашения Давай мы
sorting it out  these Minsk agreements
начнём разбирать эти минские соглашения
you I said I said that you are draining the salt you
ты Я сказал я сказал что ты соль ты
see you
сливаешь види
won’t find it in your life You won’t
не в жизни не найдёшь Ты в жизни не
find the Minsk agreements in your life you have never
найдёшь минские соглашения ты никогда их
opened them in life
не открывал в
So
жи Вот
far the Minsk agreements that
пока минские соглашения которые
begin with the
начинаются со
media
СМИ
bend Dawa Constitutions And you have a
согни Дава Конституции А у тебя есть
Constitution Come on  you
Конституция Давай ты
stesh you stesh you can’t find the Minsk
стеш ты стеш ты не можешь найти минские
agreements Find the Minsk
соглашения Найди минские
agreements this is a set of measures to
соглашения это комплекс мер по
implement the Minsk agreements let’s
выполнению минских соглашений давай
find the Minsk agreements And [ __ ] And in the sense of [ __ ] Well the Minsks
найди минские А [__] А в смысле бляд Ну
were a set of measures it wasn’t he was
мински были комплекс мер был не он был
after the Minsk complex the world was already in
после минских комплекс мир уже был в
December in my opinion or  that when and Minsky
декабре по-моему или что когда а Минский
was not and a
был нет
set of measures who did not fulfill the [ __ ] let's
а комплекс мер кто не выполнил бля давай
not eat the Minsk
не есть минские
agreements there are Minsk agreements Find the Minsk
соглашения есть минские соглашения Найди
agreements come on now We'll
соглашениям выпо Давай сейчас Мы про
talk about the peace complex about the Minsk said
комплекс мир поговорим о минских сказал
he specifically says the Minsk agreements
он специально говорит минские соглашени
signed so that they won't come out later Okay that's
подписал чтобы их потом не вы ло Ладно
it I  I understand, come
всё я Поня Давай
on, you're suckers, not suckers, and now you're going to [ __ ]'
ра лохи не лохи А сейчас вы бляд будете
balls, Poroshenko is on you, along with
вы шары Порошенко вас на вместе с
Merkel. Yes, you suckers took it; you stopped. You would have
Меркель Да вы лохи взяли остановились Вы
taken Kiev in 2-3 days, but you
бы взяли тогда Киев за 2-3 дня но вас
were cheated like suckers, yes. And now then you
развели как лохов да А теперь потом вы
decided to really take Kiev, they took you.  Yes,
решили реально взять Киев вас взяли в Да
I admit it, and then you were lured to Istanbul
я признаю а потом вас в Стамбул заманили
and you were cheated like suckers, you just left
и вас как лохов развели вы просто ушли
from near Kiev, you didn’t get any
из-под Киева Вы там не получили
stars there, you just left, they beat you up for the second time,
звездюлей вы просто ушли вас второй раз
you’re suckers in the square after and then
навали вы лохи в квадрате после а потом
you left the Kharkov region and then
вы ушли из Харьковской области а потом с
Kherson  because you
Херсона потому что вы
suckers Balabol
лохи Балабол
got burned let's move
подгорел идём
on I'm so god damn well damn He's spinning he
дальше я так бож акче ну блин Крутится
can't go, all he has to do is
крутится не может ити всё ж ему осталось
blow up his ass and yell you didn't
потом взорвать пердак и орать вы не
do it Poroshenko And so on to continue
выполнили Порошенко И так дальше
to throw it on yes I mean the dude damn school
накидывать да то есть чувак блин школу
no no this school curriculum doesn't
не не этот школьную программу не
understand and  here he starts to get into
понимает и тут начинает лезть типа в
such wilds, not class Class I
такие Дебри не класс Класс Мне
liked it, yes you are suckers, we deceived you
понравилось да вы лохи мы вас обманули
Yes, we deceived you with Minsk,
Да мы вас обманули с минскими со
Istanbul and Kherson, we will also
стамбульский с херсоном также мы вас
deceive you when with Crimea Yes, there will be some kind of
обманем когда с Крымом Да будет какой-то
agreement that you are leaving Crimea, in short,
договорняк что вы уходите с Крыма короче
yes Don’t run away  go away And we will do something in
да Не убегайте уходите А мы что-то там
return It is unknown what will happen yes But they
взамен Неизвестно что будет да Но вам
will tell you that we did not fulfill again
расскажут что мы не выполнили снова меня
This suits me Subscribe to my
Такое устраивает подпишись на мий
Telegram right now the axis of wine and
Telegram прямо зараз ось вин а
popk tse even more and even more politely YouTube
попк це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube
drives on through srg or ny ban and even
загоняет на через срг ор ньй бан и дуже
richer video  I don’t show people at all times
багато вдео не показую людям вчасно не
the information about the stream. That’s why
показуе информация про стрими Тому для
I need to write a Mali operational link
того щоб ми Мали оперативний звязок
right away, but in the meantime, in Telegra,
пишиться прямо зараз а пок там в телегра
Okrim video is still tsikava and korisna
окрим видео ще теж цикава и корисна
information and we are guilty of you trima
информация и мы повинни з вами трима
postiyny operational link, in addition,
постийний оперативный звязок незалежно в
show you the process YouTube  Glory to
того чи покаже вам проце YouTube Слава
Ukraine
Украине
write
пиши